so
good afternoon everyone i'm adrika
and now it's finally time for our next
question
question number four of the day so in
total
it will be our 44th question so now
without
any further ado let's just quickly
uh start with our question let's just
quickly start discussing our question so
here is the question on the screen so
you have been driving for 10 hours
straight
to reach your destination which is still
30 kilometers away
when you feel drowsy and tired
you will a safely park
and rest for 15 to 20 minutes b
reach destination first to get
sound and uninterrupted sleep
c drink energy drink and continue
or
a
and rest for 15 to 20 minutes
b reach destination first to get sound
and
uninterrupted sleep c energy
uh drink energy drink and continue
or d take medicines and continue
[Music]
to get uninterrupted
so you know this is our question and i
will
uh you know request all of you to answer
this question as
uh you know
you will
[Music]
on
can answer this question and become a
part of
us so you know you can
answer this become a part of us which is
like really
amazing
is
but still our roads are not
safe
[Music]
you know what will
so i will just uh once again repeat this
question
so you have been driving for
10 hours straight to reach your
destination
which is still 30 kilometers away
when you feel drowsy and tired
you will a safely park and rest
for 15 to 20 minutes b
reach destination first to get sound and
uninterrupted sleep see drink
energy drink and continue or d
take medicines and continue so i'll just
once again
repeat this question in hindi also so
[Music]
you know i will request all of you to
answer this question as well as the
other questions which will be coming
and then the rest of the questions rest
of the questions
five five new questions will be coming
tomorrow also so you know
or you know it's
[Music]
you know you can
rules in a forum and
why we should take part in this
uh you know like this questions like
this they will be coming
every two hours uh rose
[Music]
and you know you can simply answer this
and it doesn't take a lot of your time
also
right up your link description
doesn't take a lot of your time also so
you know uh it's really great to be a
part of this camera
it is sorry benefits
[Music]
of thinking
so you know always follow the rules for
our own safety
so now i will just once again repeat
this question
uh you have been driving for 10 hours
straight or to reach your destination
which is still 30 kilometers away
when you feel drowsy and tired
you will a safely park
and rest for 15 to 20 minutes b
reach destination first to get
sound and uninterrupted sleep or c
drink energy drink and continue
[Music]
you know just think like that and answer
this question
and become a part of this
become a part of this uh you know it is
really easy to answer uh you know you
can bring
or from our youtube page or facebook
page and the results
uh you know every day at 10 pm we have a
show called bluntly speaking
the results will be announced there as
well as the answers will also be
discussed there only so uh you can just
see the results as well as answers there
and also or up
or up to your results
baby things up there so you know it's
really simple
so i will request all of you to become a
part of this
bring the change and take one more step
and take one more step ahead to make our
roads
safer thank you everyone